[
  {"index":1,"Question":"一口食べる","Answer":"take a bite"},
  {"index":2,"Question":"怪しい","Answer":"That's sketchy"},
  {"index":3,"Question":"怯える","Answer":"get frightened"},
  {"index":4,"Question":"問題を起こす","Answer":"make waves"},
  {"index":5,"Question":"急ごう","Answer":"Step on it."},
  {"index":6,"Question":"手こずる","Answer":"have a hard time"},
  {"index":7,"Question":"もういくね","Answer":"I'm off"},
  {"index":8,"Question":"寝る","Answer":"get some sleep"},
  {"index":9,"Question":"返す","Answer":"give it back"},
  {"index":10,"Question":"全力を尽くせ！","Answer":"Give it your all!"},
  {"index":11,"Question":"気だるい","Answer":"languid"},
  {"index":12,"Question":"取り乱す","Answer":"get upset"},
  {"index":13,"Question":"一か八かやってみる","Answer":"take a chance"},
  {"index":14,"Question":"しくった","Answer":"Shoot"},
  {"index":15,"Question":"似ている","Answer":"take after"},
  {"index":16,"Question":"濡れる","Answer":"get wet"},
  {"index":17,"Question":"準備する","Answer":"get ready"},
  {"index":18,"Question":"二度寝した","Answer":"I went back to sleep"},
  {"index":19,"Question":"参加するよ","Answer":"Count me in."},
  {"index":20,"Question":"わかる(have)","Answer":"have a clue"},
  {"index":21,"Question":"軽視する","Answer":"take lightly"},
  {"index":22,"Question":"嫌じゃなければ","Answer":"If you don't mind"},
  {"index":23,"Question":"電話に出る","Answer":"get a call"},
  {"index":24,"Question":"一休みする","Answer":"have a rest"},
  {"index":25,"Question":"仲直りする","Answer":"make up"},
  {"index":26,"Question":"どうもありがとう","Answer":"Many thanks"},
  {"index":27,"Question":"からかう","Answer":"make fun of"},
  {"index":28,"Question":"検討する","Answer":"go over it"},
  {"index":29,"Question":"どっちでもいいよ","Answer":"Both are good"},
  {"index":30,"Question":"黙って","Answer":"Zip your lip."},
  {"index":31,"Question":"どうしよう","Answer":"I'm lost"},
  {"index":32,"Question":"オファーをする","Answer":"make an offer"},
  {"index":33,"Question":"どうして？","Answer":"How come?"},
  {"index":34,"Question":"取り外す","Answer":"take it off"},
  {"index":35,"Question":"分解する","Answer":"take apart"},
  {"index":36,"Question":"何となく","Answer":"Just because."},
  {"index":37,"Question":"手術する","Answer":"have an operation"},
  {"index":38,"Question":"間に合う","Answer":"make it"},
  {"index":39,"Question":"例えば？","Answer":"Like what?"},
  {"index":40,"Question":"引き継ぐ","Answer":"take it over"},
  {"index":41,"Question":"風邪をひく","Answer":"get a cold"},
  {"index":42,"Question":"話し合う","Answer":"have a talk"},
  {"index":43,"Question":"選択肢がある","Answer":"have an option"},
  {"index":44,"Question":"家に帰る","Answer":"get home"},
  {"index":45,"Question":"ぜひ！","Answer":"By all means"},
  {"index":46,"Question":"お大事に","Answer":"Take care"},
  {"index":47,"Question":"みる","Answer":"have a look"},
  {"index":48,"Question":"わからない","Answer":"I have no idea"},
  {"index":49,"Question":"頭痛がする","Answer":"have a headache"},
  {"index":50,"Question":"自信がある","Answer":"have confidence"},
  {"index":51,"Question":"できれば","Answer":"If possible"},
  {"index":52,"Question":"着替える","Answer":"get changed"},
  {"index":53,"Question":"散歩する","Answer":"take a walk"},
  {"index":54,"Question":"久しぶり","Answer":"It's been a while"},
  {"index":55,"Question":"ふりをする","Answer":"make believe"},
  {"index":56,"Question":"もしよければ","Answer":"If you want"},
  {"index":57,"Question":"もうやってられない","Answer":"I'm done!"},
  {"index":58,"Question":"早く良くなってね","Answer":"Get well soon!"},
  {"index":59,"Question":"小便する","Answer":"make water"},
  {"index":60,"Question":"座る","Answer":"have a seat"},
  {"index":61,"Question":"難しい","Answer":"have difficulty"},
  {"index":62,"Question":"私機嫌が悪い","Answer":"I am in a bad mood"},
  {"index":63,"Question":"クビになる","Answer":"get fired"},
  {"index":64,"Question":"もう一度言って？","Answer":"Come again"},
  {"index":65,"Question":"酔っ払う","Answer":"get drunk"},
  {"index":66,"Question":"〇〇を思い切り楽しむ","Answer":"make the most of 〇〇"},
  {"index":67,"Question":"シャワーを浴びる","Answer":"take a shower"},
  {"index":68,"Question":"暗くなる","Answer":"get dark"},
  {"index":69,"Question":"怪我ない？","Answer":"Are you injured?"},
  {"index":70,"Question":"機会を得る","Answer":"get a chance"},
  {"index":71,"Question":"決断する","Answer":"make a decision"},
  {"index":72,"Question":"意味をなす","Answer":"make sense"},
  {"index":73,"Question":"落ち着いて","Answer":"calm down"},
  {"index":74,"Question":"お腹が空く","Answer":"get hungry"},
  {"index":75,"Question":"コメントする","Answer":"make a comment"},
  {"index":76,"Question":"間違える","Answer":"make a mistake"},
  {"index":77,"Question":"危ない！","Answer":"watch out!"},
  {"index":78,"Question":"結婚する","Answer":"get married"},
  {"index":79,"Question":"メモを取る","Answer":"take notes"},
  {"index":80,"Question":"影響がある","Answer":"have an effect"},
  {"index":81,"Question":"怒る","Answer":"get angry"},
  {"index":82,"Question":"試験を受ける","Answer":"take an exam"},
  {"index":83,"Question":"道に迷う","Answer":"get lost"},
  {"index":84,"Question":"確かめる、必ず〇〇する","Answer":"make sure"},
  {"index":85,"Question":"気軽に行こうよ","Answer":"Take it easy"},
  {"index":86,"Question":"離婚する","Answer":"get divorced"},
  {"index":87,"Question":"薬を飲む","Answer":"take medicine"},
  {"index":88,"Question":"寝坊した","Answer":"I overslept."},
  {"index":89,"Question":"休憩する","Answer":"take a break"},
  {"index":90,"Question":"きも","Answer":"Eww"},
  {"index":91,"Question":"昼寝をする","Answer":"take a nap"},
  {"index":92,"Question":"評判","Answer":"reputation"},
  {"index":93,"Question":"かゆい","Answer":"itchy"},
  {"index":94,"Question":"可能性","Answer":"possibility"},
  {"index":95,"Question":"さっき","Answer":"just now"},
  {"index":96,"Question":"要求","Answer":"request"},
  {"index":97,"Question":"一言言う","Answer":"have a word"},
  {"index":98,"Question":"大事にする","Answer":"make much of"},
  {"index":99,"Question":"もうちょっとやったのに","Answer":"I almost had it!"},
  {"index":100,"Question":"需要","Answer":"demand"},
  {"index":101,"Question":"専門知識","Answer":"expertise"},
  {"index":102,"Question":"変だ","Answer":"weird / odd"},
  {"index":103,"Question":"さすが！","Answer":"As expected"},
  {"index":104,"Question":"へ向かう","Answer":"I head to"},
  {"index":105,"Question":"いい雰囲気","Answer":"have a nice vibe"},
  {"index":106,"Question":"気まずい","Answer":"awkward"},
  {"index":107,"Question":"まじで、ほんまに","Answer":"literally"},
  {"index":108,"Question":"〇〇に向き合う","Answer":"face"},
  {"index":109,"Question":"何となく","Answer":"Just because."},
  {"index":110,"Question":"意外と","Answer":"than I thought"},
  {"index":111,"Question":"どうしたらいい？","Answer":"What should I do?"},
  {"index":112,"Question":"お先どうぞ","Answer":"Go ahead"},
  {"index":113,"Question":"気にしないで","Answer":"Don't sweat it."},
  {"index":114,"Question":"それなら","Answer":"In that case,"},
  {"index":115,"Question":"〇〇しないで、","Answer":"Instead of"},
  {"index":116,"Question":"行かなきゃ","Answer":"Gotta go."},
  {"index":117,"Question":"音上げて","Answer":"Turn it up"},
  {"index":118,"Question":"同感","Answer":"I’m with you."},
  {"index":119,"Question":"別に","Answer":"Nah"},
  {"index":120,"Question":"注目の話題","Answer":"hot topic"},
  {"index":121,"Question":"柔軟な考え方","Answer":"open mind"},
  {"index":122,"Question":"優しい嘘","Answer":"white lie"},
  {"index":123,"Question":"街の男","Answer":"local guy"},
  {"index":124,"Question":"たまたま〇〇する","Answer":"happen to 〇〇"},
  {"index":125,"Question":"一応言っておく","Answer":"just saying"},
  {"index":126,"Question":"念の為にね","Answer":"Just in case."},
  {"index":127,"Question":"取り返す","Answer":"get it back"},
  {"index":128,"Question":"やり遂げる","Answer":"go through with it"},
  {"index":129,"Question":"全体的に、総じて","Answer":"altogether"},
  {"index":130,"Question":"火をつける","Answer":"light the fire"},
  {"index":131,"Question":"間違って","Answer":"by mistake"},
  {"index":132,"Question":"承知しました","Answer":"Noted."},
  {"index":133,"Question":"承知しました","Answer":"Certainly"},
  {"index":134,"Question":"もちろん！","Answer":"Absolutely!"},
  {"index":135,"Question":"まさにそう","Answer":"Exactly"}
]